# RICHARD B. HALL

# **Professional Summary**

Administrative professional and full stack web developer with five years of experience working in a fast-paced office environment. Proficient with HTML5, CSS, and Javascript and coding databases. Extensive knowledge of sales, payroll, purchasing, and human resources. Experience coordinating with dozens of employees within the operations of a large organization.

# **Professional Work Experience**

# Texas Concrete / Feb 2017 - May 2020

Operations Support - Feb 2018- May 2020

- Managed 90 employees' timecards, working with our payroll department to complete weekly audits
- Onboarded new drivers with equipment distribution, tablet configuration, and information entered in our software programs
- Maintained stock and disseminated Personal Protective Equipment (PPE) for five plant locations in central Texas
- Placed orders for PPE, tools, office supplies, and equipment for our batch offices and Quality Control department
- Created, tracked, and followed up with quotes for prospective construction clients up to \$10,000,000
- Provided technical support for multiple information systems and devices including driver tablets and computers.

#### Administrative Assistant - Feb 2017- Feb 2018

- Corresponded with clients regarding material and service price increases
- Documented disciplinary action taken against drivers
- Coordinated food and drinks for company ready-mix plants
- Assisted with adjusting employees' daily timecards
- Created training videos for proper use of new equipment
- Completed various clerical tasks as needed

# Office of the Attorney General / Oct 2015 - Oct 2016

# Administrative Assistant I October 2014-October 2016

- Answered and redirected calls to attorneys
- Created and formatted bound copies of legal documents
- Compiled reports of extensive requested documents
- Distributed daily mail and packages
- Proofread and redacted legal documents
- Aided in requested administrative tasks

#### Contact

(210) 800-3046 www.github.com/HallRB www.linkedin.com/in/HallRB Richardbrianhall@gmail.com

## Education

University of Maryland 2010-2014
B.A. Theatre
B.A. Classical Literature and Languages

University of Texas Austin Coding Bootcamp Certificate for Full Stack Web Development

#### Skills

- Front-end web development, creating practical applications and interactive web pages with extensive CSS styling.
- Advanced experience using Microsoft Office Suite
  - Using formulas and pivot tables for tracking, calculating, and managing data in Excel
- Creating and tracking quotes and bids with iSqFt and Salesforce software
- Comfortable with public speaking and communicating with clients, contractors, and colleagues in a solution-oriented manner
- Confident completing large and complex tasks by set deadlines
- Comprehensive understanding of Adobe Photoshop and AVS Studios for photo and video editing.

## References

#### **UT Coding Bootcamp**

Tariq Abusheikh and/or Owais Jamil –
Bootcamp Instructors (Pending)

#### Texas Concrete

Rodney McCarn – General Manager Rodney.mccarn@txconcrete.com (512) 217-1403